Guide to the Greenwich House Records TAM.139
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Administrative Records
  - Subseries D: Property Records
    - Sub-subseries 6: 27 Barrow Street
      - 29-31 Barrow Street- Building Inspections, 1914, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 33)
      - 27 Barrow Street- Building Specifications, 1916 (Box 7, Folder 34)
      - 27 Barrow Street- Floor Plans, 1916 (Box 7, Folder 35)
      - 27 Barrow Street- Contracts, 1916 (Box 7, Folder 36)
      - 27 Barrow Street- Sidewalk Trees, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Sub-subseries 7: 28 Macdougal Street
      - 28 Macdougal Street Property & Rent Correspondence (Richmond Hill House), 1925-1931 (Box 7, Folder 38)
      - 28 Macdougal Street- Sale (Richmond Hill House), 1929 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Sub-subseries 8: Midland Beach, Staten Island
      - Midland Beach, Staten Island Cottage Correspondence, 1927-1942 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Sub-subseries 9: Various properties -- history of acquistion
      - Properties- History of Acquisition and Prices, 1920-1934 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Subseries E: Personnel Records
    - Sub-subseries 1: Paid Workers
      - Paid Workers' Applications A-Z, 1922-1942 (Box 7, Folder 42)
      - WPA- Workers Applications A-Z, 1934-1942 (Box 7, Folder 43)
        Reel 10 (MN# 2191)
      - WPA- National Youth Administration Workers- Applications, 1936-1938 (Box 7, Folder 44)
      - WPA Workers- Lists of Workers with Activities and Schedules, 1935-1936, undated (Box 7, Folder 45)
      - Personnel Policies, 1937-1946 (Box 7, Folder 46)
      - Staff Rosters with brief resumes, undated (Box 7, Folder 47)
      - Staff Rosters, 1927-1929 (Box 7, Folder 48)
      - Staff Rosters, 1930-1938 (Box 7, Folder 49)
      - Staff Rosters, 1941-1944 (Box 7, Folder 50)
      - Staff Rosters with Job Descriptions, 1941-1942 (Box 7, Folder 51)
      - Abrams, Dorothy, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 52)
      - Antoun, Nora, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 53)
      - Atlee, William, 1935-1939 (Box 7, Folder 54)
      - Baker, Helen, 1939-1941 (Box 7, Folder 55)
      - Baker, William, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 56)
      - Barden, Elizabeth, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 57)
      - Baretta, Helen, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 58)
      - Barr, William, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 59)
      - Bartholemew, Elizabeth, 1924 (Box 7, Folder 60)
      - Benvenuto, Perino Harold, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 61)
      - Boozer, Mary, 1936-1938 (Box 7, Folder 62)
      - Brown, Elizabeth, 1936-1940 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Bunting, Natalie, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Butler, Miriam, 1930-1932 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Byron, Mrs, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Callisi, Claudius, 1929 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Campbell, Ian, 1939-1941 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Capobianco, Mildred, 1925 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Carpenter, Mary, 1921-1932 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Cawthon, Margaret, 1926 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Carvellone, Josephine, 1939-1940 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Chase, Alice, 1927-1929 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - Chase, Mary, 1921 (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - Clegg, John, 1932 (Box 8, Folder 13)
      - Cline, Hazel, 1929-1932 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - Cockburn, Kathleen, 1924-1935 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - Colby, Ruth, 1928-1932 (Box 8, Folder 16)
      - Collins, Gertrude, 1917-1940 (Box 8, Folder 17)
      - Connor, Ernest, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 18)
      - Cook, Warren, 1932-1934 (Box 8, Folder 19)
      - Cooke, Simon, 1929 (Box 8, Folder 20)
      - Cooney, Mary, 1926-1927 (Box 8, Folder 21)
      - Cordani, Thelda, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 22)
      - Crane, Vernon, 1938-1939 (Box 8, Folder 23)
      - Crawford, Suzanne, 1919-1927 (Box 8, Folder 24)
      - Crockett, Marian, 1932 (Box 8, Folder 25)
      - Cromwell, Oliver, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 26)
      - Crosby, Isabel, 1937-1939 (Box 8, Folder 27)
      - Crout, Reva, 1923 (Box 8, Folder 28)
      - Crowder, James, 1921-1922 (Box 8, Folder 29)
      - Cuneo, Erminia, 1917-1941 (Box 8, Folder 30)
      - Daversa, Benjamin, 1923-1924 (Box 8, Folder 31)
      - Dearbom, Isabelle, 1921 (Box 8, Folder 32)
      - dePhillips, Isabella, 1939-1941 (Box 8, Folder 33)
      - deRogatis, Edith, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 34)
      - Dickerman, Marian, 1922-1923 (Box 8, Folder 35)
      - Diehl, Alice, 1929 (Box 8, Folder 36)
      - Diggs, Thomas, 1921-1923 (Box 8, Folder 37)
      - Dobson, Pansy, 1929-1942 (Box 8, Folder 38)
      - Dohery, Franes, 1929 (Box 8, Folder 39)
      - Donlin, Mike, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 40)
      - Dorsey, William, 1933-1935 (Box 8, Folder 41)
      - Dorsey, William, 1938-1939 (Box 8, Folder 42)
      - Douglas, Kirk, 1939-1940 (Box 8, Folder 43)
      - Dreyer, Zoa, 1929-1930 (Box 8, Folder 44)
      - Drollman, Marion, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 45)
      - Droogan, Charlotte, 1923-1928 (Box 8, Folder 46)
      - Duke, Madge, 1925-1926 (Box 8, Folder 47)
      - duVall, Everett, 1922-1923 (Box 8, Folder 48)
      - Earle, Marion, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 49)
      - Eddy, Marguerite, 1925-1926 (Box 8, Folder 50)
      - Edgar, Stanley, 1929-1930 (Box 8, Folder 51)
      - Eisenbrey, Robert, 1940-1941 (Box 8, Folder 52)
      - Elliott, Elizabeth, 1934-1942 (Box 8, Folder 53)
      - Ewing, Manford, 1929-1930 (Box 8, Folder 54)
      - Falgiano, Victor, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 55)
      - Feil, Ara Mary, 1921 (Box 8, Folder 56)
      - Fennick, John, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 57)
      - Feverstein, Frances, 1939-1940 (Box 8, Folder 58)
      - Fielder, Catherine, 1932 (Box 8, Folder 59)
      - Fields, Susan, 1930 (Box 8, Folder 60)
      - Fitzpatrick, Alice, 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 61)
      - Foother, Marjorie, 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 62)
      - Forgione, Anthony, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 63)
      - Fox, Mark, 1929 (Box 8, Folder 64)
      - Franklin, Janice, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 65)
      - Gaets, Dorothy, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 66)
      - Galowich, Maximilian, 1939-1940 (Box 8, Folder 67)
      - Garbarino, Elizabeth, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 68)
      - Garcia, Mary, 1939-1941 (Box 8, Folder 69)
      - Gerhardt, Adam, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 70)
      - Gibson, Robert, 1929-1931 (Box 8, Folder 71)
      - Gilbert, Lawrence, 1929 (Box 8, Folder 72)
      - Gilliam, Margaret, 1926-1931 (Box 8, Folder 73)
      - Gilman, Charles Malcolm, 1922-1926 (Box 8, Folder 74)
      - Giovine, Marie, 1929-1930 (Box 8, Folder 75)
      - Gisi, Dorothy, 1923 (Box 8, Folder 76)
      - Gobetti, John P, 1931-1932 (Box 8, Folder 77)
      - Goldin, Philip, 1941-1942 (Box 8, Folder 78)
      - Goller, Gertrude, 1941-1942 (Box 8, Folder 79)
      - Goldstien, Bertha, 1939-1941 (Box 8, Folder 80)
      - Goreth, Gertrude, 1926 (Box 8, Folder 81)
      - Gouveia, Rose, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 82)
      - Green, Dorothy, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 83)
      - Grumpelt, Helen, 1932-1933 (Box 8, Folder 84)
      - Grunzweig, Judith, 1941-1942 (Box 8, Folder 85)
      - Hargrave, Eleanor, 1939-1941 (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - Haviland, Marion, 1923-1926 (Box 8, Folder 87)
      - Henderson, William, 1939-1942 (Box 8, Folder 88)
      - Hermans, James, 1940-1941 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Howard, Lois, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Howell, Ethel, 1922-1923 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Howley, Dolores, 1940 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Hyman, Barney, 1923-1929 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Jeffrey, Howard, 1939-1940 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Jenkins, Ruth, 1937 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - Jewett, Josephine, 1923-1930 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - Johnson, Helen, 1930-1934 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - Johnson, Hester, 1909-1939 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - Johnston, Anna Belle, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - Johnston, Barbara, 1933-1934 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - Kapela, William, 1941-1942 (Box 9, Folder 13)
      - Kazon, Elia, 1933 (Box 9, Folder 14)
      - Keller, Laura, 1929-1930 (Box 9, Folder 15)
      - Keller, Ruth, 1930-1933 (Box 9, Folder 16)
      - Kevill, Katharine, 1925-1926 (Box 9, Folder 17)
      - Kingdon, Mabel, 1928-1930 (Box 9, Folder 18)
      - Kissock, Amy, 1933-1934 (Box 9, Folder 19)
      - Kirchner, Katherine, 1926-1927 (Box 9, Folder 20)
      - Kline, Evelyn, 1940 (Box 9, Folder 21)
      - Klosky, Rosilyn, 1940-1941 (Box 9, Folder 22)
      - Kramer, Edith, 1941-1942 (Box 9, Folder 23)
      - Krein, Harvey, 1932-1935 (Box 9, Folder 24)
      - Krom, Roscoe, 1939-1940 (Box 9, Folder 25)
      - Kuder, Merle, 1930-1931 (Box 9, Folder 26)
      - Lange, Louis, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 27)
      - Lancier, Ruby, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 28)
      - LaRocca, John, 1938-1939 (Box 9, Folder 29)
      - Lea, Alice, 1929-1931 (Box 9, Folder 30)
      - Leap, Daniel, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 31)
      - LeBon, Lorraine, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 32)
      - Lees, Ruth, 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 33)
      - Leibold, Elizabeth, 1927-1929 (Box 9, Folder 34)
      - Leslie, Alice, 1928-1931 (Box 9, Folder 35)
      - Levander, Rena, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 36)
      - Levi, Helen, 1938-1940 (Box 9, Folder 37)
      - Levinson, Dorothy, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 38)
      - Levy, Jennie Lind, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 39)
      - Lewis, Mary, 1923-1926 (Box 9, Folder 40)
      - Lewis, Winifred, 1922-1924 (Box 9, Folder 41)
      - Lierfallom, Jarle, 1938-1941 (Box 9, Folder 42)
      - Linn, Helen, 1930-1934 (Box 9, Folder 43)
      - Longanecker, Elizabeth, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 44)
      - Lord, Katherine, 1921 (Box 9, Folder 45)
      - Lubbe, Maja, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 46)
      - Lustig, Charlotte, 1939-1940 (Box 9, Folder 47)
      - Lutz, Dorothy, 1924-1926 (Box 9, Folder 48)
      - Maas, Lynette, 1926-1927 (Box 9, Folder 49)
      - MacDowall, Ellen, 1920-1939 (Box 9, Folder 50)
      - MacIver, Betty, 1938-1939 (Box 9, Folder 51)
        Reel 11 (MN# 2192)
      - MacIver, Evertt, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 52)
      - Malach, John, 1939-1941 (Box 9, Folder 53)
      - Mann, Fannie, 1924-1925 (Box 9, Folder 54)
      - Manucia, Charles, 1941-1942 (Box 9, Folder 55)
      - Manson, Anne, 1923-1924 (Box 9, Folder 56)
      - Marsh, Flora, 1929-1932 (Box 9, Folder 57)
      - Martin, Richard, 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 58)
      - Mascio, Matilda, 1926-1930 (Box 9, Folder 59)
      - Maxwell, S. A., 1926 (Box 9, Folder 60)
      - McCann, Walter, 1925 (Box 9, Folder 61)
      - McCarthy, Edward, 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 62)
      - McCarthy, John, 1939-1940 (Box 9, Folder 63)
      - McCaughan, Grace, 1909-1921 (Box 9, Folder 64)
      - McDowell, Elizabeth, 1922-1932 (Box 9, Folder 65)
      - McElroy, Grace, 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 66)
      - McElroy, Mary, 1926-1929 (Box 9, Folder 67)
      - McGuire, Mathilde, 1929-1931 (Box 9, Folder 68)
      - McKee, Thistle, 1933-1934 (Box 9, Folder 69)
      - McKenna, Frank, 1933-1934 (Box 9, Folder 70)
      - McMahon, Gertrude, 1922-1926 (Box 9, Folder 71)
      - McManus, Joseph, 1934-1935 (Box 9, Folder 72)
      - McNall, Lucy, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 73)
      - McReady, Pauline, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 74)
      - Meredith, W. F., 1929-1930 (Box 9, Folder 75)
      - Metcalf, Richard, 1940 (Box 9, Folder 76)
      - Meyer, Olive, 1929-1930 (Box 9, Folder 77)
      - Miceli, Francis, 1930-1931 (Box 9, Folder 78)
      - Miffin, Alice, 1931 (Box 9, Folder 79)
      - Milano, Joseph, 1922-1926 (Box 9, Folder 80)
      - Milch, Ernest, 1940-1941 (Box 9, Folder 81)
      - Miller, Helen, 1929-1930 (Box 9, Folder 82)
      - Miller, Mary, 1925-1926 (Box 9, Folder 83)
      - Mims, Levinia, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 84)
      - Minor, Elsie, 1927-1932 (Box 9, Folder 85)
      - Monteverdi, Lewis, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 86)
      - Moore, Mrs. Alfred, 1930-1931 (Box 9, Folder 87)
      - Moore, Lola, 1940 (Box 9, Folder 88)
      - Moore, Merriam, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 89)
      - Morsell, Mary, 1924-1926 (Box 9, Folder 90)
      - Munno, Anna, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 91)
      - Murray, Hazel, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 92)
      - Murray, Thomas, 1939-1940 (Box 9, Folder 93)
      - Nellis, Louise, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 94)
      - Nichols, Edna, 1925 (Box 9, Folder 95)
      - Nizolek, Frank, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 96)
      - Northrup, Egbert, 1937-1941 (Box 9, Folder 97)
      - Oliver, Beatrice, 1917-1941 (Box 9, Folder 98)
      - Oliver, Mildred, 1931-1932 (Box 9, Folder 99)
      - O'Neil, John E., 1929-1930 (Box 9, Folder 100)
      - Opp, Arthur, 1940 (Box 9, Folder 101)
      - Oppenheimer, Dorothy, 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 102)
      - Oscarson, Ruby, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Othmer, Joseph, 1928-1932 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Owen, Lester, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Paige, Mary & Sheral, 1923-1927 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Pantzer, Margaret, 1939-1941 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Paris, Patsy, 1930-1931 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Parsell, Alfred, 1940 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Passerini, Louis, 1933-1934 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Patton, Julia, 1929 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Peters, Margaret, 1938-1941 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Pelly, Farrell, 1924-1925 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Phelps, Nellie, 1929 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Phillips, Gladys, 1940-1941 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - Picariello, John, 1940 (Box 10, Folder 14)
      - Poole, Mary, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 15)
      - Popolizio, Emanuel, 1933-1934 (Box 10, Folder 16)
      - Potter, Olive, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 17)
      - Prouty, Ida, 1941-1942 (Box 10, Folder 18)
      - Raffo, Victor, 1926-1942 (Box 10, Folder 19)
      - Raup, Gustavus, 1928-1942 (Box 10, Folder 20)
      - Reed, Louis, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 21)
      - Reeves, William, 1931-1932 (Box 10, Folder 22)
      - Reilly, Grace, 1928-1929 (Box 10, Folder 23)
      - Richards, Gretchen, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 24)
      - Ringe, Helen, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 25)
      - Robinson, Maude, 1910-1942 (Box 10, Folder 26)
      - Rogers, Helen, 1930-1931 (Box 10, Folder 27)
      - Rogers, Henrietta, 1925-1928 (Box 10, Folder 28)
      - Rosett, Louise, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 29)
      - Ryan, Harold, 1915 (Box 10, Folder 30)
      - Ryan, Harriet, 1930-1932 (Box 10, Folder 31)
      - Ryan, Marguerite, 1938-1939 (Box 10, Folder 32)
      - Ryan, Mary, 1932-1933 (Box 10, Folder 33)
      - Ryder, Lois Leonard, 1941-1942 (Box 10, Folder 34)
      - Sachs, Murray, 1930-1932 (Box 10, Folder 35)
      - Samuels, Muriel, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 36)
      - Saphir, Robert, 1940-1941 (Box 10, Folder 37)
      - Saunders, Vera, 1940-1941 (Box 10, Folder 38)
      - Schirone, Adele, 1940-1941 (Box 10, Folder 39)
      - Schmidt, Theodora, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 40)
      - Schwab, Herbert, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 41)
      - Segar, George, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 42)
      - Selden, Nathan, 1930-1932 (Box 10, Folder 43)
      - Servoss, Maude, 1931-1932 (Box 10, Folder 44)
      - Sembler, Alice, 1926-1928 (Box 10, Folder 45)
      - Shafer, Alice, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 46)
      - Shanks, Blanche, 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 47)
      - Shemelia, Mrs. Isaac, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 48)
      - Sherman, Eleanor, 1935-1936 (Box 10, Folder 49)
      - Sherman, Sarah, 1929-1930 (Box 10, Folder 50)
      - Shropshire, Eileen, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 51)
      - Siedman, Mary, 1939-1941 (Box 10, Folder 52)
      - Smith, Kenneth, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 53)
      - Smith, Mae, 1930-1931 (Box 10, Folder 54)
      - Smith, Romaine, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 55)
      - Spaeth, Dorothea, 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 56)
      - Spotts, Hollis and Alwin, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 57)
      - Stolper, Virginia, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 58)
      - Sugar, Richard, 1941-1942 (Box 10, Folder 59)
      - Sullivan, Anne, 1932-1933 (Box 10, Folder 60)
      - Sutherland, Louis, 1941-1942 (Box 10, Folder 61)
      - Sweetser, Emily, 1938-1939 (Box 10, Folder 62)
      - Swift, Ruth, 1931-1932 (Box 10, Folder 63)
      - Swing, Elizabeth, 1937-1939 (Box 10, Folder 64)
      - Tendler, Diana, 1940-1941 (Box 10, Folder 65)
      - Tibbitts, Mary, 1927-1929 (Box 10, Folder 66)
      - Timlow, Emily, 1931-1932 (Box 10, Folder 67)
      - Tomasone, Rafaela, 1938-1945 (Box 10, Folder 68)
      - Torrens, Iva, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 69)
      - Toth, Julia, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 70)
      - Trella, Louis, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 71)
      - Twohy, Marguerite, 1927-1929 (Box 10, Folder 72)
      - Veazie, Emily, 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 73)
      - Venitt, Gertrude, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 74)
      - Vorn, Rhoda, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 75)
      - Wagner, William, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 76)
      - Wallace, Nancy, 1939-1942 (Box 10, Folder 77)
      - Ware, Caroline, 1930-1932 (Box 10, Folder 78)
      - Watt, Richard, 1940 (Box 10, Folder 79)
      - Weaver, Persis, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 80)
      - Webb, Cleaver, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 81)
      - Webb, George, 1931-1932 (Box 10, Folder 82)
      - Whitlock, Susam, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 83)
      - Whitworth, Virginia, 1929-1931 (Box 10, Folder 84)
      - Wiggins, Dorothy, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 85)
      - Wilbur, Darl, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 86)
      - Wiley, June, 1935 (Box 10, Folder 87)
      - Wilson, Emma, 1929 (Box 10, Folder 88)
      - Wilson, Darcy, 1929-1930 (Box 10, Folder 89)
      - Welp, Elizabeth, 1941-1942 (Box 10, Folder 90)
      - Wolfe, Lucy, 1940-1941 (Box 10, Folder 91)
      - Woodard, Henry, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 92)
      - Wright, Ann, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 93)
      - Ziegler, Emmanuel, 1936-1938 (Box 10, Folder 94)
      - Zimmer, Erich, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 95)
      - Znaiden, Marie, 1939-1940 (Box 10, Folder 96)
    - Sub-subseries 2: Residents
      - Resident/House Member Biographies, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Residents' Volunteer Assignments, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Residents' Applications, 1922-1944 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Aanestad, Elling, 1932 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Abrich, Sadie, 1933 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Adams, Emma, 1917 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Adams, Irving, 1930 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Ahrens, Henriette K., 1933 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Alden, Lydia, 1923 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Alfred, Helen, 1923-1926 (Box 11, Folder 10)
        Reel 12 (MN#2193)
      - Altpeter, Stanford, 1929-1930 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - Ambler, Laura, 1922-1923 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      - Anderson, Evelyn, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - Anderson, Martha, 1924-1926 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - Andrews, Edna, 1934 (Box 11, Folder 15)
      - Arnold, Margaret, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 16)
      - Autenrieth, Olga, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 17)
      - Bailey, Dorothy, 1931-1932 (Box 11, Folder 18)
      - Bastow, Robert, 1935 (Box 11, Folder 19)
      - Batting, Elizabeth, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 20)
      - Bedinger, George, 1920-1922 (Box 11, Folder 21)
      - Beebe, Emily, 1935 (Box 11, Folder 22)
      - Benham, Isabel, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 23)
      - Bergquist, Laura, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 24)
      - Berstl, Nora, 1929-1930 (Box 11, Folder 25)
      - Bevis, Margaret, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 26)
      - Biermann, Berthold, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 27)
      - Biklen, Mildred, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 28)
      - Blackburn, Rebecca, 1931-1932 (Box 11, Folder 29)
      - Blake, Alice, 1933-1934 (Box 11, Folder 30)
      - Blatt, Cecilia, 1930 (Box 11, Folder 31)
      - Boone, Gladys, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 32)
      - Boubnoff, Nicholas, 1932 (Box 11, Folder 33)
      - Bourne, Grace, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 34)
      - Brennemann, Mary, 1930 (Box 11, Folder 35)
      - Breshnan, Ann, 1933-1934 (Box 11, Folder 36)
      - Brewer, Donald, 1935 (Box 11, Folder 37)
      - Bridgman, Margaret, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 38)
      - Brierly, Marguerite, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 39)
      - Briscoe, Lura, 1930-1931 (Box 11, Folder 40)
      - Brooks, Barbara, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 41)
      - Brophy, Alice, 1935 (Box 11, Folder 42)
      - Brougher, Elizabeth, 1928-1929 (Box 11, Folder 43)
      - Brown, Edith, 1931-1932 (Box 11, Folder 44)
      - Brown, Eleanor, 1924-1926 (Box 11, Folder 45)
      - Brown, Jeanette, 1929 (Box 11, Folder 46)
      - Brownell, Jean and Sara, 1934-1935 (Box 11, Folder 47)
      - Buckley, Jane, 1936-1937 (Box 11, Folder 48)
      - Bulkley, Margaret, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 49)
      - Burroughs, Lisle, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 50)
      - Burrows, Angeline, 1931-1934 (Box 11, Folder 51)
      - Bush, Imogen, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 52)
      - Butterworth, Virginia, 1934 (Box 11, Folder 53)
      - Callicut, Julia, 1930 (Box 11, Folder 54)
      - Campbell, Dorcas, 1927-1934 (Box 11, Folder 55)
      - Campbell, John, 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 56)
      - Carlsrud, Gertrude, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 57)
      - Carritt, Gabriel, 1931-1932 (Box 11, Folder 58)
      - Carroll, Ray, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 59)
      - Chadwick, Eileen, 1932 (Box 11, Folder 60)
      - Chamberlain, Norman, 1923-1924 (Box 11, Folder 61)
      - Cherry, Sara, 1932 (Box 11, Folder 62)
      - Chickering, Adelle, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 63)
      - Chitambat, Theodore, 1931-1932 (Box 11, Folder 64)
      - Clark, Hope, 1934-1935 (Box 11, Folder 65)
      - Clark, Martha, 1936 (Box 11, Folder 66)
      - Clark, Pauline, 1926-1927 (Box 11, Folder 67)
      - Clements, Sara, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Cochran, Mary, 1926 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Coffin, Rosamond, 1931 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Coffman, Ramon, 1923-1928 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Coman, Jean, 1933-1934 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Comegy, Gretchen, 1925 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Connor, George, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Cook, Gardner, 1936-1939 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Cook, Warren, 1932-1934 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Courow, Anne, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Cowper, Christine, 1930 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - Cozzens, Bertha, 1921-1922 (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - Cramer, Ernest, 1939-1940 (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - Craton, Margaret, 1925 (Box 12, Folder 14)
      - Cummings, Caroline, 1929 (Box 12, Folder 15)
      - Dalsimer, Florence, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 16)
      - Daniel, Mary, 1925-1931 (Box 12, Folder 17)
      - Davied, Camille, 1924-1925 (Box 12, Folder 18)
      - Davies, John Langdon, 1924-1925 (Box 12, Folder 19)
      - Davis, Evelyn, 1923 (Box 12, Folder 20)
      - Davis, Gertrude, 1923 (Box 12, Folder 21)
      - deBernardi, Mathilde, 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 22)
      - Debevoise, Katherine, 1923 (Box 12, Folder 23)
      - deJarecki, Tadevsz, 1921-1922 (Box 12, Folder 24)
      - deSantis, Joseph, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 25)
      - deSchwenitz, Dorothea, 1926 (Box 12, Folder 26)
      - Dew, Elizabeth, 1924-1926 (Box 12, Folder 27)
      - Dietrichson, Dagny, 1936 (Box 12, Folder 28)
      - Diller, Helen, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 29)
      - Dinwiddie, Courtenay, 1923 (Box 12, Folder 30)
      - Doane, Frank, 1923, 1941-1944 (Box 12, Folder 31)
      - Dorin, Denise, 1921 (Box 12, Folder 32)
      - Doty, Margaret, 1938-1940 (Box 12, Folder 33)
      - Dougall, Else, 1926 (Box 12, Folder 34)
      - Downing, Ruth, 1930 (Box 12, Folder 35)
      - Downward, James, 1929 (Box 12, Folder 36)
      - Drowne, George, 1934-1935 (Box 12, Folder 37)
      - deBellis, Daniel, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 38)
      - Drummond, Agnes, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 39)
      - Dudrow, Dorothy, 1931 (Box 12, Folder 40)
      - Dunlap, Henrietta, 1923-1931 (Box 12, Folder 41)
      - Dunlap, Josephine, 1934-1935 (Box 12, Folder 42)
      - Durnell, Ethel, 1931 (Box 12, Folder 43)
      - Duy, Lila, 1923-1929 (Box 12, Folder 44)
      - Dyer, Katherine, 1929-1930 (Box 12, Folder 44A)
        Reel 13 (MN# 2194)
      - Earhart, Amelia and A.O. (mother), 1928-1930 (Box 12, Folder 44B)
      - Eisenbrandt, Marie, 1926 (Box 12, Folder 45)
      - Eliot, Samuel, 1926 (Box 12, Folder 46)
      - Emery, Jewel, 1926-1927 (Box 12, Folder 47)
      - Ensor, Olivia, 1937-1939 (Box 12, Folder 48)
      - Evans, Sid, 1925-1929 (Box 12, Folder 49)
      - Farnham, Rita, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 50)
      - Faulkes, Marie, 1921-1922 (Box 12, Folder 51)
      - Faulkner, Frederic, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 52)
      - Feely, Clare, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 53)
      - Fisher, Angeline, 1921 (Box 12, Folder 54)
      - Fitzgerald, Geneva, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 55)
      - Fitzgerald, Marie, 1937-1938 (Box 12, Folder 56)
      - FitzMorris, Richard, 1929 (Box 12, Folder 57)